atmail.com 2012-12-21

# Atmail - Privacy

### Why do we collect your personal information?

Collecting your information is essential for us to provide our products and services to you. It also helps us to understand your needs, enabling us to provide you with a greater quality of service.

Back to Top

* * *

### How do we collect personal information?

We only collect information when you knowingly provide it. Collection may include requesting information by phone, filling out a contact/registration/purchase form on check-in, providing your business card to us, or e-mailing or faxing us your details.

Back to Top

* * *

### Do we disclose your personal information to anyone?

We may disclose your personal information where you have consented to us doing so. We may also be required or authorised by law to disclose your personal information. We also use 3rd party services to track anonymous usage of the Atmail website along with technical details exposed by your web browser. Atmail's use of Google AdWords Remarketing Lists may use a cookie to target marketing material to you on Google and other third-party sites across the Internet. Should you wish, you can opt out of this target by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). If you provide us with your email address, we will add you to our email mailing list managed by Campaign Monitor ([view Campaign Monitors's privacy policy](http://www.campaignmonitor.com/privacy/)). If your email client allows, your interactions with our newsletters will be tracked for marketing purposes. Occasionally we ClickTale to track detailed usage of our marketing website and product demos ([view ClickTale's privacy policy](https://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx)). [Opt-out of ClickTale](http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html).

Back to Top

* * *

### Is your personal information up-to-date?

It is important that the personal information we collect is accurate, complete and up-to-date. You can contact us at any time to update your personal information, or to tell us if your personal information is inaccurate or incomplete.

Back to Top

* * *

### Is your personal information secure?

We take all reasonable precautions to safeguard your personal information from misuse, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. When your information is no longer required we securely destroy it from our systems.

Back to Top

* * *

### Can you access your personal information?

You may request access to the information we hold about you by contacting us. We may be required by law to retain your personal information after you have ceased your relationship with us.

Back to Top

* * *

### What about sensitive information?

Sensitive information can be about racial or ethnic origin, membership of a profession or trade, personal health or other personal information. We only collect, use or disclose sensitive information about you as is allowed by law.

Back to Top

* * *

### Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time.

We constantly review our policies and procedures to keep up-to-date with changes in law, technology and the needs of our guests and we may change this policy from time to time.

Back to Top

* * *

## Can you complain about a breach of your privacy?

You may lodge a concern or complaint with us by writing to the General Manager. For additional information on privacy visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's website: [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/).

Back to Top
